Let's get this patty started.
The Bob's Burgers Movie is a animation, music, comedy
film directed by Bernard Derriman.
When a ruptured water main creates an enormous sinkhole right in front of Bob's Burgers, it blocks
the entrance indefinitely and ruins the Belchers’ plans for a successful summer.
While Bob and Linda struggle to keep the business afloat, the kids try to
solve a mystery that could save their family's restaurant.
As the dangers mount, these underdogs help each other find hope and
fight to get back behind the counter, where they belong.
Bob Belcher / Jimmy Jr. / Ms. Labonz (voice), played by H. Jon Benjamin.
Louise Belcher (voice), played by Kristen Schaal.
Linda Belcher / Jocelyn (voice), played by John Roberts.
Tina Belcher (voice), played by Dan Mintz.
Gene Belcher (voice), played by Eugene Mirman.
Teddy (voice), played by Larry Murphy.
The Bob's Burgers Movie is a 2022 American animated musical comedy film
based on the animated sitcom created by Loren Bouchard.
Directed by Bouchard and series director Bernard Derriman and written by Bouchard and Nora
Smith, the original voice cast from the series reprise their roles, including H.
Jon Benjamin, Dan Mintz, Eugene Mirman, Larry Murphy, John Roberts,
Kristen Schaal, David Wain, Zach Galifianakis, and Kevin Kline.
Set between the 12th and 13th seasons of Bob's Burgers, the plot follows Bob and his family's struggles with paying their loan after a
sinkhole opens in front of their restaurant and affects business, while the kids try to solve the murder of a carnie.
The Bob's Burgers Movie premiered at the El Capitan Theatre in Hollywood on May 17, 2022, and was theatrically released by 20th
Century Studios in the United States on May 27, following previous delays of almost two years due to the COVID-19 pandemic.
The film received positive reviews from critics, but only
grossed $34 million against a $38 million budget.
The film explores themes of test of courage, crime scene,
aftercreditsstinger, based on tv series, secret playroom.
The tone is lighthearted and mind_bending.